David R Jex

1343 Bandera Hwy
Apt 210
Kerrville, TX 78028
256-738-0090
david.jex@me.com

PROFILE

Intelligent, well spoken, dedicated, with innovative problem solving skills, a resourceful young man who is striving to work on a career. Is certified as a Greenway trainer and has experience with software, managing projects, and leading teams of people acquired by working as a contractor and an analyst for both Greenway and Peterson Regional Medical Center. Experienced with public speaking after serving a mission for the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints in the Samoa, Apia Mission as well as developing good people skills. Strong work ethic and determination to succeed.

EXPERIENCE

2014-Present · Greenway Analyst · Peterson Regional Medical Center · Kerrville, TX

I provided training on PrimeSuite for clinical and billing staff. I managed projects and worked with other departments to implement a bi-directional interface with the hospital EMR Meditech, created a query to pull out referrals created and export them to a drop box to be picked up by another vendor, and handled the transition to version 17.10 and the conversion of templates to be ICD-10 compatible. I worked with vendors to meet deadlines for implementing new functionality and upgrades such as implementing Medfusion, Direct Messaging, Immunization Registries, and the Specialty Registry. I helped the providers to meet MU requirements and provide information for audits. I developed workflows for better utilization of PrimeSuite including editing templates and working with the staff to develop better processes. I also developed reports for recording financial, patient, and practice data. I have also been trained on Financial Intelligence for running, subscribing, and editing report contained within the product. I have worked closely to with Greenway support to resolve issues such as superbly edits, bugs, and miscellaneous problems.

2012-2014 · Contractor/Implementation Specialist · Greenway Medical Technologies · Carrolton, GA

Provided training on EMR for clinical staff, organized team implementations, and assessed training needs for sites for several hospital sites and healthcare systems. Set up sites on e-perscribe.

2010-2012 · Security Officer · Securitas · Bessemer,AL

Secure site location for all employees. Responsible for overseeing incoming deliveries as well as prescription drug deliveries.

2009-2010 · Utility Preperation · Jack's Family Resturaunt · Alabaster, AL

Provided customer service and collaborated with all teammates.

2007-2008 · Sales Representative · Party America · Littleton,CO

Provided service to customers as well as supported management with all operation of the business.

EDUCATION

2008 · Dakota Ridge High School, Littleton, CO · High School Diploma

SKILLS

I am proficient in HTML5, CSS, and Javascript. I have a knowledge of the clinical workings of hospitals and private practices acquired through many years of working with EMR's. I have experience with setting up providers and filing proper paperwork for e-perscribe. I can speak conversational Samoan. I have training in CPR and emergency First Aid. I learn quickly and take pride in my work. I am a fluent public speaker. I am organized and can manage multiple projects.

REFERRALS

Richard Cruthirds 2014 - Present Chief Information Officer

(830) 258-7100

Mark Thomason 2014- Present Operations Manager

(830) 258-7100

Connie Whiting 2014- Present Practice Manager Kerrville Pediatrics

(830) 257-1440

Paula Collins 2012-1013 Resource Manager

770-624-4113

Allan Coker 2012-2013 Project Manager

678-839-4246